# Nitin Pathuri

Andhra Pradesh, India



pathurinitin@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/nitin-pathuri

## Summary

Experienced Managing Editor with a demonstrated history of working in the animation industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, Strategic Planning, and Microsoft Office. Strong media and communication professional graduated from Little flower school Guntur.

### **Experience**



#### Jeevan Kaushal club editor

KITS Jeevan Kaushal May 2022 - Present (1 month +)

# Managing Editor

madnit

Aug 2015 - Present (6 years 10 months +)

### **Education**

KKR&KSR Institute of Technology & Sciences, VINJANAMPADU Village (CC-JR)

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Data science Aug 2020 - Jan 2024

### Sri Chaitanya College of Education

Intermediate, Maths and Science Mar 2018 - Apr 2020

#### Little flower school Guntur

Bachelor's degree, Tenth 2007 - 2018

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Introduction to Programming Using Python - HackerRank 331E2CD101BA

# Problem solving skills - HackerRank

BC5C06913B92

# Data Analysis Using Python - IBM



AWS Academy Graduate - AWS Academy Data Analytics - Amazon Web Services (AWS)

## **Skills**

kungfu • Microsoft Office • Management • Customer Service • Microsoft Excel • Project Management • Leadership • Microsoft Word • Strategic Planning • Microsoft PowerPoint